{
    "subject": "resource/Jamais_(song)",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "resource/Connie_Francis",
    "human_readable": "The artist of the song Jamais is Connie Francis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9169360995292664,
            "question": "Is Connie Francis known for singing Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8851169347763062,
            "question": "Name a song sung by Connie Francis."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.849515438079834,
            "question": "Who is the artist who sang the song Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8136788010597229,
            "question": "What is the name of the song performed by Connie Francis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5278142690658569,
            "question": "Can you name another popular song by Connie Francis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4359808564186096,
            "question": "What is the story behind the song Jamais?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36436113715171814,
            "question": "When was the song Jamais released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3549130856990814,
            "question": "What other musical talents does Connie Francis possess besides singing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34522339701652527,
            "question": "What genre is the song Jamais likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29622194170951843,
            "question": "Has Connie Francis won any awards for her singing?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of the song Jamais is Connie Francis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1716_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the song Jamais likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1716_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other musical talents does Connie Francis possess besides singing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1716_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the song Jamais released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1716_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1716_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports the triple that Connie Francis is an artist who has performed a song called \"Jamais\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not mention that Connie Francis performed any songs titled \"Jamais\". The provided texts discuss her career highlights, music influence, and current status but do not reference a specific song by this title."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Connie Francis' discography is not provided or mentioned in the context information, thus there is no evidence to support that she sings a song named \"Jamais.\"",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Several pieces of text state that Connie Francis was a popular singer in the late 1950s and early 1960s, with hits like \"Stupid Cupid,\" \"Who's Sorry Now,\" and \"Where The Boys Are.\" There is no mention of her singing a song called \"Jamais.\"",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not mention Connie Francis performing or recording a song called \"Jamais.\" Furthermore, her recent activities are described as being more focused on supporting military veterans and residing in Florida, with no indication of active performances.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}